it seems like and current society how you have been excessively concerned with ar
看起来和当前社会，您如何过分关注ar
self-image with even though i might think my fingers
即使我可能会想到我的手指也有自我形象
or even old is this really the case of you just show and the world and or even
甚至老了，这确实是您所展示的情况以及整个世界，甚至
more reflection or how the sewer how the bears to your shirt and repression
更多的思考或下水道如何影响衬衫和镇压
Paris or even there and that pilots service there heights a monster that maico
巴黎甚至那里，那里的飞行员都在高处服务于魔鬼
weeks sunday
周日
festival thank you for your paypal donation and thank you card size boring and
节感谢您的贝宝捐赠，并感谢您的卡大小无聊的恩
alexander for supporting the op patreon a push it very much
亚历山大非常支持推特
and it helps me to continue this project well let's drive and no matter where you
它可以帮助我继续进行这个项目，无论您身在何处，
are constantly be fine and redesigned to be really a and at the same time each
一直都很好，并重新设计为真正的
other people's behavior in society how do you respect it
他人在社会上的行为您如何尊重它
to be given shirt and be the ratio chili acceptable
被给予衬衫并且辣椒比例可以接受
armani code of conduct and systems of fx doe fss society in workplaces at home in
阿玛尼在家中工作场所的fx doe fss社会行为守则和系统
night live in a restaurant at the party's either by consequence
晚上在聚会的一家餐馆住
that how there is ever a number of girls who care sets of behaviors
那有多少女孩关心一系列行为
beliefs about myself and how they relate to the world
关于我自己以及他们与世界的关系的信念
thatcher mascus cult de persons hats word person comes from a problem with de
撒切尔人马斯客教派崇拜的人的帽子人这个词来自于德的问题
people is that many people percent m even one
人是百分之一的人，甚至一个人
shirt and be who you are many and that sarbot already in one places of the village
衬衫，成为您的一员，那个sarbot已经在村庄的一个地方了
the mind this happens consciously sometimes
头脑有时会有意识地发生
unconsciously switch zeitguide I knew cult from a young age
我不知不觉就切换了Zeitguide，从小就知道
the dark places the shadow [Music]
黑暗中有阴影[音乐]
what kind of freccia gnome shadow is that many people don't even know that they
什么样的狂躁症侏儒阴影是很多人甚至不知道他们
have a specially box with a very strong attachment to their person a who
有一个特别的盒子，对他们的人有很强的依恋
believe he labor persona and it the possibly can all be something else but
相信他是劳作角色，这可能全是别的东西，但是
am working in the dark yes they might experience on photos and
在黑暗中工作，是的，他们可能会在照片上遇到和
designers de rock quiet and convenient to be quickly wordpress them
设计师de rock安静，方便，可以快速将它们压印
with the murders push the larger and tumblr the shadow biekamp unquote
与谋杀案一起推动更大和更大的阴影biekamp unquote
jong unfortunately there can be no doubt that men could then i
遗憾的是，容格毫无疑问的是，男人可以做到这一点。
imagine simself to us to be a free one carries a shadow
想象自己对我们成为一个自由的人会留下阴影
and the lesson is and bodies in the individual's chances live the black there and
教训是，个人机会中的尸体在那里生活着黑色，
centuries and quote and I sample of death ardie of us
几个世纪以来，我引用了我们对死亡的狂热
scandal sweet and religious and spirit show communities shirt and positions spot
丑闻甜蜜，宗教和精神秀社区衬衫和位置现货
box about priest limping holy men and so warm or three choir
关于牧师行圣人的盒子，如此温暖或三声合唱
behavior that is natural control has long been going on with the social expectation
长期以来，自然控制的行为一直伴随着社会的期望
that they be havens shuttle race you know holy my new regrets
他们是避风港的梭子赛跑，你知道，圣洁，我的新遗憾
successful ie wat der zwan who haven't been able to integrate
成功，例如无法整合的wat der zwan
er en design built right after a while these bubbels of repressed designer
不久之后，这些受压抑的设计师们纷纷冒充他们的设计
start to chest and shadow that dave wordpress for jurs
开始迷恋WordPress的胸部和阴影
oh dear decades comes to the service and not and friendly way people with
哦，亲爱的几十年来服务，而不是友好的人
dance shadow's ear or an extreme dj mental
舞影的耳朵或极端的dj心理
at wordpress der flash and arrow has a quick to just works at lido lock in
在wordpress der上闪动，而箭头则可以快速地在对Lido锁定时起作用
reality dc in otherwise what i tried to hide and even at project in arlon
否则，我试图隐藏甚至在阿尔隆的项目中的现实DC
darkness on two mothers how you at least don't have to look into
两个母亲的黑暗，你至少不必去研究
the abs or eurolines with the more education of seeing
有更多的见识的腹肌或欧元
product designer and other people is assigned to be white he work to do
产品设计师和其他工作人员被分配为白人
even though i'd be hey pesticides since the toilet and neighbors
即使自厕所和邻居以来我都会杀虫剂
go to work by the societal rules summer deep inside their works and in
夏季，按照社会规则去上班，深入工作
mens capacity for evil
男人的邪恶能力
world war 2 is a great example of how innocent readily people can turn into
第二次世界大战是一个很好的例子，说明人们如何轻易地将无辜变成
bloodthirsty killers picasso furious of unfortunate events on
毕加索嗜血杀手大怒，发生不幸事件
monster rose of the germ a collective en consciousness and masters x-force there
细菌的怪物玫瑰上升了集体意识，并在那里掌握了x力
is malice other chips all over the world that led to one of the largest
是导致世界上最大的恶意芯片之一的恶意芯片
massacres in the history of mankind s young cities
人类年轻城市历史上的屠杀
the change of character is big on
性格的改变是一个大错误
the operation of collective oriental agree a sing-along a gentle and race
东方集体的运作与轻柔和种族相呼应
normal being can be transformed into a maniac
正常人可以转化为狂人
of savage beast bonus already inclined to members blame on external circumstances
野兽奖金的增加已经倾向于成员应归咎于外部环境
but nothing could exploit en as if it had not been there and quote
但是没有什么可以利用en的，就好像它还没有出现过一样并引用
how quiet or trouble comprehending this to they probably cause those photos
对他们的理解有多安静或麻烦，可能会导致这些照片
accepting a dark side and rather videography crimes committed tess en
接受阴暗的一面，而宁愿摄影犯罪
evil that is a push and sam religions they play outside force is like spirits
邪恶是推力，他们在外力作用下的山姆宗教就像灵魂
or the devil what's confused breaks out more ahh
或魔鬼的困惑更多爆发了啊
certain that you won't be a monster
确定你不会成为怪物
where is an extreme i stamp arno so lets get closer to home if you think
我到底在哪里邮票阿诺，所以如果你认为的话，让我们离家更近些
of yourself so good or evil right person may be given some sort of such a person
对自己如此善良或邪恶的人可能会给予某种此类的人
that can't each other's how to live how broad age fitness already is
彼此之间不能如何生活已经有多大年龄适合
therefore they loved ones capes way ow does charity's
因此，他们所爱的人披着斗篷走慈善之路
celebrated by his or her environment for being such wonderful person have you
以他或她的环境而庆祝，因为他是一个如此出色的人
ever entertain the possibility that biology service you might actually
曾经接受过这样的可能性，即您实际上可能会提供生物学服务
be a huge jerk that behind the mask
在面具后面是一个巨大的混蛋
harrison up linus it used in hiding for so long and john don't even know where
哈里森一直藏在莱纳斯上很久了，约翰甚至不知道在哪里。
it or perhaps you all what you give us to see it could be the reason that it
它或也许是您给我们的所有东西让我们看到了，这可能是其原因
seems to take some much effort to be that fantastic person they mnd old and the
似乎需要付出很多努力才能成为那个他们老了的出色人，
nice detail the moor internal conflict you seem to feel good it be that the priest is
漂亮的细节，您似乎感觉很好，是因为牧师是
actually a control freak that the trillion avalanche orchestra isn't already doing it
实际上是一个控制怪胎，即万亿雪崩乐团还没有做到这一点
for fame and the driver spurgeon guru is only in it for the money
为了成名，司机司布真大师只是为了钱
whatever i person and the reasons hotel people
无论我个人和酒店人的原因
wiley pursuant to pursue the most likely hehe de intentions
威利遵循最可能的意图
note who doesn't want to look at and has the side you want the service in
请注意谁不想看，但有想要您提供服务的一面
mediate had to am back down the german scully's intentions
调解必须撤退德国人的意图
thank winter for ellen was spoke about is or too cold and winter
谢谢冬天，因为艾伦曾被谈论过，或者冬天太冷了
thanks is a photo www in the back of you might
谢谢你后面的照片www
santing national deep down but can set met
深入国民，但可以满足
and quote the fingers at being aware of argentor we see that there
并引用手指以了解阿根廷人，我们看到那里
something insiders it we do a show treeworld what
有什么内幕吗，我们做一个展示Treeworld的事情
heavily influenced is our actions also by looking closeup shot en jump
受到很大影响的是，我们的动作也通过查看特写镜头进行跳转
judgments about other people who might identify the exact thanks wiki pins in
关于其他人的判断，这些人可能会确定确切的Wiki PIN码
the shadow carl jung experiences become anybody
影子卡尔·荣格的经历变成了任何人
aware of eyeshadow and finally to integrate it personally were
意识到眼影并最终将其个人化
less likely to lose control over the carillon
不太可能失去对钟琴的控制
poses process individual whites 3 reconciliation of all aspects of there
构成个人白人3那里各个方面的和解
persons who and coloring the villages was so baby
那些给村庄上色的人真是宝贝
how jar it may feel that to mitigate website we shouldn't
减轻网站负担可能会带来多大的震撼，我们不应该
wordpress at what we should do is make in the unconscious
我们应该做的是在无意识中制造wordpress
butts the shadow thousand is container negative left
暗影千头是集装箱负向左
join the earth you may have wordpress certain aspects of yourself
加入地球，您可能会压抑自己的某些方面
like creativity or sexual interest that society siesta blue thinks that can be
就像社会午睡蓝色认为的创造力或性兴趣
address only if you acknowledge vote when brave enough to shed light on to
仅当您在足够勇敢的时候承认投票时才发言
the darkness and look by another person a deadly percent to the world and free day
黑暗和另一个人的目光，对世界和自由的日子造成了致命的伤害
a week and start to work with the shadow and [ __ ] benefit from its
一个星期，并开始与阴影和母狗一起工作，受益于它
power and see the beauty and art imperfections s psychologist mary en wit
力量，看到美与艺术的不完美，心理学家玛丽·恩威特
my side night is espressions ssd
我的相伴之夜是ssd
thank you for watching
谢谢你的收看
[Music]
[音乐]